[
	{
		"question": "What is a shark's skeleton made of?",
		"options": [
			"Bone",
			"Cartilage ",
			"Titanium",
			"Keratin"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What does a stingray use for defence",
		"options": [
			"Toxic Substances",
			"Venomous Spine",
			"Poisonous Tail",
			"Sharp Tooth"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What are thermohaline currents?",
		"options": [
			"Cold water currents from the arctic",
			"Warm water currents from Africa",
			"Currents that move up and down in the ocean",
			"Currents from the equator"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "What are the main categories of sea life?",
		"options": [
			"Swimmers and non-swimmers",
			"Fish, mammals and microscopic creatures",
			"Fishes and plants",
			"Swimmers, floaters and creatures on the sea floor"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "What type of water is more dense?",
		"options": [
			"Equator, hot water",
			"Polar, cold water",
			"Water close to the shore",
			"Deep sea water"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What sea life is at the very bottom of the food chain?",
		"options": [
			"Microscopic fish",
			"Corals",
			"Algae",
			"phytoplankton"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Which is the fish that can inflate its body to up to three times its normal size?",
		"options": [
			"Pufferfish",
			"Octopus",
			"Sunburst anthias",
			"Seahorse"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Which saltwater fish has a snout can grow up to one-third its entire body length?",
		"options": [
			"Swordfish",
			"Bullethead rockskipper",
			"Leaping bonito",
			"Toadfish"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Which is the deepest oceanic trench?",
		"options": [
			"Tonga Trench",
			"Mariana Trench",
			"Kermadec Trench",
			"Japan Trench"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "How much heart(s) does an octopus have?",
		"options": [
			"One",
			"Two",
			"Three",
			"Four"
		],
		"answer": 2
	}
]